(Priya:)There is no assigned seats,
Sheldon.
(Priya:)Just sit anywhere.
Make yourself comfortable.
(Sheldon:)Oh, what fun.
(Sheldon:)We're like hippies at a love-in.
(Leonard:)Just sit here.
(Sheldon:)Right on, man. Right on.
(Sheldon:)Oh, look.
it's Harry Potter and 98%
of The Sorcerer's Stone.
(Raj:)Okay, we've
got fajitas
(Raj:)with all the fixins,
so you make your own.
(Sheldon:)Wonderful.
(Sheldon:)Dinner, some
assembly required.
(Priya:)Do you want a margarita,
Sheldon?
A margarita?!
Where are we?!
What is happening?!
(Penny:)Oh. Hey, Sheldon.
What can I get you?
(Sheldon:)Water. Neat.
(Sheldon:)With a little umbrella.
(Penny:)Where are all your friends?
(Sheldon:)Sadly, Penny, this evening,
I am the Dark Knight,
(Sheldon:)roaming these
mean streets alone.
(Sheldon:)A windbreaker for my cape,
(Sheldon:)and a stern expression
for my cowl.